export const quizMedio = [
  {
    question: "COMIDA FAVORITA",
    options: ["pizza", "pasta", "pollo"],
    correct: [1, 2],
  },
  {
    question: "BEBIDA DE SIEMPRE",
    options: ["latte", "agua", "frappe"],
    correct: [1],
  },
  {
    question: "SERIES FAV GIRLY",
    options: [
      "gossip girl, pretty little liars",
      "gilmore girls",
      "pretty little liars, gilmore girls",
    ],
    correct: [0],
  },
  {
    question: "EMOJI DE SIEMPRE",
    options: ["coraz√≥n rosita", "destellos", "ambos"],
    correct: [2],
  },
  {
    question: "ELIGE MI FAVORITO",
    options: ["Barbie", "Monster High", "Bratz"],
    correct: [0],
  },
  {
    question: "MI LUGAR FAVORITO",
    options: ["playa", "campo", "ciudad"],
    correct: [0],
  },
  {
    question: "CANCION FAV DE ARIANA",
    options: ["Love Me Harder", "Put Your Hearts Up", "Everyday"],
    correct: [0],
  },
  {
    question: "ANIMAL FAVORITO",
    options: ["delfin", "mariposa", "ambos"],
    correct: [2],
  },
  {
    question: "TOP DE ARTISTAS",
    options: [
      "Ariana, Rihanna, Chainsmokers, Calvin Harris, Little Mix, Halsey, Taylor y Dua Lipa",
      "Ariana, Selena, Rihanna, Taylor, Martin Garrix, Katy Perry, Bebe Rexa, Charlie XCX",
      "Ariana, Dua Lipa, Rihanna, Taylor, Kygo, Calvin Harris, Selena, Twenty One Pilots",
    ],
    correct: [0],
  },
  {
    question: "SERIE FAVORITA",
    options: ["El Internado", "Bajo Sospecha", "Control Z"],
    correct: [0],
  },
];